locklip.com 2017-12-21

# Privacy Policy - Locklip

The use of the Locklip.com website(s) and/or Locklip.com software and any Locklip.com services and products (collectively, the “Website”) provided by Locklip.com (“Locklip.com”) are subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy, including any amendments or updates hereto. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Locklip.com [Terms & Conditions](http://locklip.com/terms-and-conditions/). If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website.

**Privacy Statement for the Locklip.com Web Site**

Your privacy is important, so we’d like to explain what information we collect when you visit Locklip.com ([http://www.locklip.com](http://www.locklip.com/)), why we collect it and how it is used. We’d also like to explain your options to access and control your information, our data security practices and other matters. This Policy is governed by our [Site Terms](http://locklip.com/terms-and-conditions/).

**Special Note About Children**

Locklip.com is not intended for children, especially kids under 13. Children may use Locklip.com only with the direct supervision of their parent.

We do not seek to collect personal information about children under 13 years of age through Locklip.com. If we discover such information, we will delete it. Thus, we typically retain no information about children. However, if a parent requests a review of information we may have on their child and in the unlikely event we still retain such information and haven’t deleted it, then we will honor that request. In order to request a review or deletion of personal information that Locklip.com may have collected about your child, please email or write: <http://locklip.com/contact-us/>

When you communicate with Locklip.com, we make every effort to ensure your privacy and safety. As an added precaution, however, we still encourage parents to monitor their child’s use of the Internet, and to help us protect their privacy by reminding them never to exchange personal information with this or any other web site without the assistance or express written permission of a parent or other responsible adult.

What Information Do We Collect From You? Why?

**We May Profile You Individually.**

We may build a profile of your online habits, interests and activities when you use Locklip.com. This profile is linked to your personal identity. We compile individual profiles from “real world” contact information (e.g., street address, phone/fax), email addresses, data relating to a specific purchase, information about user PCs (e.g., IP address or browser type), data showing usage of interactive features (e.g., search engine queries), demographic information (e.g., gender, marital status, age, income, job), the personal preferences of users (i.e., favorite color, music, books), user content (e.g., message board postings), and we use these profiles for the purposes described below (please scroll down to each topic for details).  
We May Collect Information Needed to Contact You Later:

If we collect personal contact information (as described below), you may later have us modify or remove it from our system, but you may not access the information yourself.

**We May Collect Your Name, Address and Phone Number.**

When you use Locklip.com, we may request your name, street address, telephone number or other “real world” contact information. This information may reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. We use this information to complete and support the immediate activity requested, administer and run Locklip.com, customize and personalize content to your request, improve Locklip.com for everyone, tailor an instant offer to you during your visit, build a profile of your habits, interests or activities to treat you as an individual, build individual profiles for ongoing research, analysis and reporting, comply with laws requiring preservation of social histories, and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be aggregated with similar data in a manner that does not reveal your personal identity and may be disclosed only to our staff and to our immediate agents who are contracted to keep information they receive as part of their assistance to Locklip.com confidential.

**We May Collect Your Email Address.**

We may request your email address or other information needed to contact you online. This information may reveal who you are or be linked to you personally. We use it to complete and support the immediate activity requested, administer and run Locklip.com, customize and personalize content to your request, improve Locklip.com for everyone, tailor an instant offer to you during your visit, build a profile of your habits, interests or activities to treat you as an individual, build individual profiles for ongoing research, analysis and reporting, comply with laws requiring preservation of social histories, and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be aggregated with similar data in a manner that does not reveal your personal identity and may be disclosed only to our staff and to our immediate agents who are contracted to keep information they receive as part of their assistance to Locklip.com confidential.

**We May Collect Other Kinds of Information from You:**

When you use Locklip.com, we may collect personal information about you described below. You may later have us modify or remove the information, but you may not access the information yourself.

**We May Collect Information About Your Computer.**

When you visit Locklip.com, we may automatically collect information about your computer configuration, such as your browser type, operating system, IP address or ISP domain name. In some cases, this information may reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. We use this information to complete and support the immediate activity requested, administer and run Locklip.com, customize and personalize content to your request, improve Locklip.com for everyone, tailor an instant offer to you during your visit, build a profile of your habits, interests or activities to treat you as an individual, build individual profiles for ongoing research, analysis and reporting, comply with laws requiring preservation of social histories, and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be aggregated with similar data in a manner that does not reveal your personal identity and may be disclosed only to our staff, immediate agents, and to our partners and affiliates who are contracted to keep information they receive as part of their assistance to Locklip.com confidential.

**We May Collect Interactive Data.**

You may decide to input data while using certain interactive features at Locklip.com, such as queries submitted to a search engine and so forth. This information may reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. We use this information to complete and support the immediate activity requested, administer and run Locklip.com, customize and personalize content to your request, improve Locklip.com for everyone, tailor an instant offer to you during your visit, build a profile of your habits, interests or activities to treat you as an individual, build individual profiles for ongoing research, analysis and reporting, comply with laws requiring preservation of social histories, and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be aggregated with similar data in a manner that does not reveal your personal identity and may be disclosed only to our staff, immediate agents, and to our partners and affiliates who are contracted to keep information they receive as part of their assistance to Locklip.com confidential.

**We May Collect Demographic Data About You.**

We may collect information about your demographic or social characteristics, such as gender, age and income level. This information may reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. We use this information to complete and support the immediate activity requested, administer and run Locklip.com, customize and personalize content to your request, improve Locklip.com for everyone, tailor an instant offer to you during your visit, build a profile of your habits, interests or activities to treat you as an individual, build individual profiles for ongoing research, analysis and reporting, comply with laws requiring preservation of social histories, and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be aggregated with similar data in a manner that does not reveal your personal identity and may be disclosed only to our staff, immediate agents, and to our partners and affiliates who are contracted to keep information they receive as part of their assistance to Locklip.com confidential.

**We May Keep Note of Your Personal Preferences.**

We may gather information concerning your personal likes and dislikes, such as your favorite color, taste in music, books or other Locklip.com content. This information may reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. We use this information to complete and support the immediate activity requested, administer and run Locklip.com, customize and personalize content to your request, improve Locklip.com for everyone, tailor an instant offer to you during your visit, build a profile of your habits, interests or activities to treat you as an individual, build individual profiles for ongoing research, analysis and reporting, comply with laws requiring preservation of social histories, and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be aggregated with similar data in a manner that does not reveal your personal identity and may be disclosed only to our staff, immediate agents, and to our partners and affiliates who are contracted to keep information they receive as part of their assistance to Locklip.com confidential.

**We May Collect Your Online Postings and Content.**

Certain features of Locklip.com may allow you to contribute content, such as message board postings, email messages, and the like. By its nature, this information may reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. We use this information to complete and support the immediate activity requested, administer and run Locklip.com, customize and personalize content to your request, improve Locklip.com for everyone, tailor an instant offer to you during your visit, build a profile of your habits, interests or activities to treat you as an individual, build individual profiles for ongoing research, analysis and reporting, comply with laws requiring preservation of social histories, and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be aggregated with similar data in a manner that does not reveal your personal identity and may be disclosed only to our staff, immediate agents, and to our partners and affiliates who are contracted to keep information they receive as part of their assistance to Locklip.com confidential.  
We do not monitor or gather information from queries (private messages) or private/secret channels on the IRC Network. We may monitor public channels for content but we do not collect or gather information about our users. We will not install or use modules or modify our IRCd or Services to allow our staff to spy on queries (private messages) or private/secret channels. In addition our staff will not enter channels secretly to view or log any private communications.

**Outside Sources and Web Sites**

Locklip.com contains hyperlinks to other web sites. Locklip.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites and companies.

Locklip.com may have entered into partnership and affiliation agreements with other web sites and companies. We may share aggregate information with our partners and affiliates as disclosed above. We may also transfer visitors to these web sites to provide certain features. Locklip.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these partners and affiliates web sites.

Beware that some of these partners and affiliates may utilize a design that incorporates and utilizes a virtually identical copy of Locklip.com’s graphics and layout so it may appear that you are still on Locklip.com web site if you didn’t notice the different domain name in the browser’s address bar. These partners and affiliates may collect information from you. Before collecting personally identifying information from you our partners and affiliates’ web sites that utilize this design will disclose that you are no longer on  
Locklip.com and that the web site is not subject to Locklip.com’s privacy policy.

We may use outside companies to display advertisements on Locklip.com. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process. Some of these ads maybe loaded off of these companies’ servers. While we use cookies in other parts of Locklip.com, cookies and/or web beacons received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.

**Third-party Advertising Disclosures.**

Locklip.com uses third-party advertising companies to serve some ads when you visit Locklip.com. These companies may use information about your visits to Locklip.com and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Additionally, Content.ad, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve some ads on Locklip.com. Content.ad’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Locklip.com users based on their visit to Locklip.com and other sites on the Internet.

**Certain Exceptional Disclosures and Compelled Disclosure.**

We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if we are required by law to disclose the information that you have submitted, we will attempt to provide you with notice (unless we are prohibited) that a request for your information has been made in order to give you an opportunity to object to the disclosure. We will attempt to provide this notice by email, if you have given us an email address, or by postal mail if you have entered a postal address. If you do not challenge the disclosure request, we may be legally required to turn over your information.

**What Are Cookies? Why Do We Use Them?**

Cookies are small files stored by your browser in your computer when you visit Locklip.com. We use cookies to improve Locklip.com and make it easier to use. Cookies permit us to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests for the same information. We mostly use “session cookies” that are automatically deleted after each visit. Cookies from Locklip.com can’t be read by other web sites. Most browsers will accept cookies until you change browser settings to refuse them.

**How Do We Protect Information We Collect?**

We offer secure web pages to collect certain kinds of user information and we store certain kinds of data in encrypted form. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented by Locklip.com reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

**How Long Do We Keep User Information?**

We generally keep user data on our server or in our archives for as long as we reasonably need it. We may alter this practice according to changing requirements. For example, we may delete some data if needed to free up storage space. We may keep other data for longer periods if the law requires it. In addition, information posted in a public forum could stay in the public domain indefinitely.

Data management requests are administered in an orderly manner to the extent feasible and within our direct control. Note: we have greater control over recently collected data than for archived data. Once data is removed from the system and archived, it may not be feasible to accommodate specific requests. In those cases, our general data retention policy applies.

**Your Consent To This Policy.**

By using Locklip.com, you agree to this Policy. Our [Site Terms](http://locklip.com/terms-and-conditions/) take precedence over any conflicting Policy provision.

**Legal Disclaimer**

Locklip.com operates AS-IS and AS-AVAILABLE, without liability of any kind. We are not responsible for events beyond our direct control. This Policy is governed by Estonian law, excluding conflicts of law principles. Any legal actions against us must be commenced in Tallinn, Estonia within one year after the claim arose, or be barred.

**If You Have A Privacy Question**

If you have a privacy question about Locklip.com, please email or write: <http://locklip.com/contact-us/>

Last updated: April 2017

Apr 4, 2017
